instantonlineprofits.com 2004-08-02

# The 16-Minute Speed Reading Audio Program

**How-To-Read-Faster.com**  
16-Minute Speed Reading Audio Program

Updated April 15, 2004

E&R Enterprises, LLC dba How-To-Read-Faster.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site: How-To-Read-Faster.com.

**IP Address**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site.

We also track IP addresses for purposes of enrollment and/or subscription.

**Information Collection**

E&R Enterprises, LLC dba How-To-Read-Faster.com is the sole owner of the information collected on How-To-Read-Faster.com. How-To-Read-Faster.com collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site, i.e. for membership registration, paid subscription publications and products or services.

**Information Sharing  
**  
Sharing Personal Information with Third Parties

We will never sell or give away your personal information to third parties for purposes of building contact lists, or anything of that nature, without your permission. How-To-Read-Faster.com stands firmly against any transfer of personal information for reasons of building the contact lists of third parties.

**** IMPORTANT!**

Any How-To-Read-Faster.com's member, associate or affiliate who participates in the sale of the personal information of visitors or customers, to build the contact lists of third parties, will be removed immediately, and without recourse, from any business relationship previously held with, for or by How-To-Read-Faster.com.

**Business Transition Exception**

In the event E&R Enterprises, LLC dba How-To-Read-Faster.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, or being acquired by another company, users� personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

**Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

**"Cookies"**

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. We also use cookies for tracking and properly crediting affiliates in our Membership Affiliate Program.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (such as their name and email address), unique identifiers (such as their Affiliate ID), and financial information (such as their account or credit card numbers). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications for registration in The How-To-Read-Faster.com Affiliate Program and to bill the user for products and services. Unique identifiers (such as Affiliate IDs) are collected for use as account numbers in our record system.

**Children**

How-To-Read-Faster.com does not knowingly collect or solicit personally identifiable information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe How-To-Read-Faster.com has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us at the address listed below.

**Links**

This site contains links to other sites. How-To-Read-Faster.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such Web sites. How-To-Read-Faster.com is not responsible for any content on any linked sites or for any goods or services available from them.

How-To-Read-Faster.com works hard to ensure that the information contained on our web pages is accurate, relevant and of the high quality that our visitors have come to expect.

We are aware of software that exists which will create external links from our content to what they consider to be related material, which other companies have paid to have shown. We are not responsible for the quality of this software or the nature of the material that it links to.

We emphasize that we are strictly against this form of unmoderated and unregulated link advertising and strictly prohibit its use within our site content. Outside advertising on the How-To-Read-Faster.com Web site is billed at the rate of $1000 per day.

We will pursue any infringement of this notice to the maximum extent of the law.

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (such as their email address). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

**Public Forums**

This site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

**Choice/Opt-Out  
**  
This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

You can send email to [ webmaster@How-To-Read-Faster.com](mailto:webmaster@How-To-Read-Faster.com) **Correct/Update**

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.  
email: [ webmaster@How-To-Read-Faster.com](mailto:webmaster@How-To-Read-Faster.com) **Changes to this Policy**

How-To-Read-Faster.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

**Governing law**

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by Hawaii law. If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: Kailua-Kona, Hawaii. Any costs and fees other than attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared equally by each of us.

If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the following location: Kailua-Kona, Hawaii, under the rules of the American Arbitration Association. Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any court with jurisdiction to do so.

How-To-Read-Faster.com is controlled, operated and administered entirely within Hawaii. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you may contact:

Rhondall K. Rapoza, Manager  
E&R Enterprises, LLC dba How-To-Read-Faster.com  
PO Box 2077  
Kailua-Kona, HI 96745-2077  
888-682-8608  
Office Hours: Mon-Fri, 9AM-5PM Hawaii Standard Time (ONLY) **  

**Physical Address (No mail accepted at this address):**

75-5705 Kuakini Highway  
Kailua-Kona, HI 96740
